<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Project on Dwi Putra Pamungkas</title>
    <link>https://underscore48.github.io/dwi_portfolio/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Project on Dwi Putra Pamungkas</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 10:58:08 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://underscore48.github.io/dwi_portfolio/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Property Rental Price Prediction</title>
      <link>https://underscore48.github.io/dwi_portfolio/post/project-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://underscore48.github.io/dwi_portfolio/post/project-2/</guid>
      <description>Create a tool that functions to provide rental price predictions for various properties based on the features possessed by the property. Machine learning regression model is used to predict property rental rates. Using data sets of San Francisco,CA property rental price. Code and Resources Used Python Version: 3.10.3
Packages: pandas, numpy, sklearn, math Dataset source: Datacamp case study
Processing Data After collect Dataset, I need to check and clean up the dataset to make sure no missing and anomaly values on Dataset before creating a Machine Learning model.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Credit Card Transaction Validation</title>
      <link>https://underscore48.github.io/dwi_portfolio/post/project-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://underscore48.github.io/dwi_portfolio/post/project-1/</guid>
      <description>Create a tool that has a function to evaluate and classify every credit card transaction submitted whether it is valid or fraudulent. A tool made using Machine Learning with a 100% accuracy rate to avoid fraud and laundering that can harm Customers and Bank. Using data sets published by UCI Machine Learning Repository (Credit Approval Data Set). The Machine Learning model used is Logistic Regression with parameter optimization, maximum iterations and tolerance values, using Grid Search Cross Validation to produce model with the best performance.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
